Hadassah Collection 0008.002.004
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
Hadassah
Bulk, 1968-2012
1912-2012
0008.002.004
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
2.0 Cubic feet 5 boxes
Hadassah founder Henrietta Szold and a group of like-minded women interested in Zionism and social welfare established the national Hadassah organization in 1912. Initially the new organization was known by two different names: the Women's Zionist Organization and the Daughters of Zion. However, because the founding meeting was held around the time of Purim, the organization eventually adopted the name "The Hadassah Chapter of the Daughters of Zion," The use of the name Hadassah was significant, because the name represents both strength and tradition. Hadassah is the Hebrew name of Queen Esther. Hadassah can also mean "myrtle," a plant with both biblical and literary significance. Szold had two goals in founding Hadassah. Appalled by health conditions she observed in Palestine in 1909, Szold sought to help raise health standards throughout the region. Additionally she saw this mission as a way to reinvigorate Jewish life in the United States by galvanizing Jewish women in support of the Zionist cause. Henrietta Szold visited Hartford in 1914 and addressed a group of local women. At some point thereafter (both 1914 and 1918 are celebrated as the date), the Hartford Chapter was founded. Hartford had always been a stronghold of Zionism. Over time, the Hartford chapter became one of the largest and most influential in the country. The primary activity of the Hartford chapter is to raise funds for Hadassah projects that include Hadassah hospitals, Youth Aliyah for the rescue of Jewish children from countries in crisis, the Jewish National Fund, and Young Judaea Zionist camps in the United States. Throughout the decades, the chapter has grown and split into several smaller chapters, offering a flexibility that has enabled the group to attract a variety of women of differing ages and backgrounds. The most extensive section of this collection is its Newsletters, which are fairly complete from 1968 to the present. The collection also includes a set of meeting invitations from the 1930s. Together these documents give a view of Hadassah activities over several decades.
Scope and Contents note
Collection Contents by Folder:
Connecticut Region/Miscellaneous
Connecticut Region/Newspaper clippings 1980s, 1990s
Farmington Valley Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1990s
Box 1:
A-Hartford Chapter/Programs/Hand of Healing
Hartford Chapter/Certificate for Service to Hartford Member Esther Welk
Hartford Chapter/About this collection
Hartford Chapter/Adeph Book Group
Hartford Chapter/Anniversaries
Hartford Chapter/Associates
Hartford Chapter/Awards and Honors Given
Hartford Chapter/Awards and Honors Received
Hartford Chapter/Constitution and By-Laws
Hartford Chapter/Conventions
Hartford Chapter/Correspondence
Hartford Chapter/Fundraising
Hartford Chapter/Hartford Herzlia /Miscellaneous/
Hartford Chapter/History
Hartford Chapter/Installation/All Divisions
Hartford Chapter/JNF Certificates
Hartford Chapter/JNF Certificates
Hartford Chapter/Meeting Invitations 1935-1941, plus misc.
Hartford Chapter/Membership
Hartford Chapter/Membership and Officer Lists 1940s-1980s
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1920s-1930s and undated
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1940s
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1950s
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1960s
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1970s
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1980s
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1990s
Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 2000s
Hartford Chapter/Programs/Donor
Hartford Chapter/Programs/Hadassah Medical Organization
Hartford Chapter/Programs/Hand of Healing
Box 2:
Hartford Chapter/Programs/Miscellaneous-Z
Hartford Chapter/Programs/Miscellaneous
Hartford Chapter/Programs/Youth Aliyah
Hartford Chapter/Sabbath
Hartford Chapter/Thrift Shop
Manchester Chapter/History
Manchester Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1980s-1990s
Miscellaneous Chapters in CT/Newspaper clippings
National Organization
New Britain Chapter/Correspondence
New Britain Chapter/History
New Britain Chapter/Newsletters
New Britain Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1980s, 1990s
Pyquaug Chapter (Newington, Rocky Hill, Wethersfield)/Newspaper clippings 1980s-1990s
Vanguard Program for Singles
Weddings through the Decades, October 20, 1987 (videocassette)
Winter in Natanya Program for Seniors
Young Judeans
Box 3: Newsletters, 1930s-1980s
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1930s
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1943
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1944
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1945
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1946
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1947
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1948
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1952
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1956
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1957
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1958
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1959
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1960
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1961
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1962
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1963
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1964
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1965
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1966
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1967
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1968
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1969
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1970
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1971
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1972
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1973
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1974
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1975
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1976
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1977
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1978
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1979
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1980
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1981
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1982
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1983
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1984
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1985
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1986
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1987
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1988
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1987
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1988
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1989
National Newsletters 1940s
Box 4: Newsletters
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah, 1990
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah; Name changes to Hadassah Bulletin in Nov., 1991
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1992
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1993
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1994
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1995
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1996
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1997
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1998
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1999
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2000
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2001
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2002
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2003
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2004
Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2005
Box 5: Hartford Chapter/Shopper's Guides
The Hartford Chapter of Hadassah issued a Shopper's Guide and Appointment Book every year as a fundraiser. In addition to advertisements for local businesses, the Guides also contain lists of officers and members, news about programs, and other information about Hadassah.
Shopper's Guide/
Shopper's Guide/1948-1949
Shopper's Guide/1951-1952
Shopper's Guide/1952-1953
Shopper's Guide/1955
Shopper's Guide/1957
Shopper's Guide/1957
Shopper's Guide/1958
Shopper's Guide/1958
Shopper's Guide/1959
Shopper's Guide/1960
Shopper's Guide/1960
Shopper's Guide/1961
Shopper's Guide/1962, 50th anniversary
Shopper's Guide/1965
Shopper's Guide/1967
Shopper's Guide/1968
Shopper's Guide/1968
Shopper's Guide/1969
Shopper's Guide/1970-1971
Shopper's Guide/1972-1973
Shopper's Guide/1972-1973
Photographs: See Photographs/Organizations/Hadassah
Oral Histories:
None
Scrapbooks:
None
Artifacts:
None
Oversized Materials:
Oversized documents have been photocopied and stored in the Oversize Documents/Organizations box; the copies have been incorporated into the main document collection.
Processed: Llyn Kaimowitz, 1998 Updated by Margaret Mair 2004
Photographs
Box 1: A-G
Anniversaries
Associates
Associates/party honoring David Sheketoff
Awards, 2 folders
Board of Directors, early 20th century
Board of Directors, late 20th century, see also OVERSIZE; folder is too large for box, and is on shelf next to the organization/oversize box.
Board of Directors/Presidents, 1980s
Building/interiors/1990s
Conferences
Conventions, 1990s
Donor Luncheon
Box 2: H-R
Hadassah Medical Organization/Big Gifts Dinner
Hand of Healing
Installations
Junior Hadassah
Major Gifts Dinner, 1990
Miscellaneous, 2 folders
Meetings
Membership
Membership/Kaplan, Shirlee/Miscellaneous photos from various Hadassah events and meetings, c.1970s-1990s
National Organization/H. Szold with S.S. Wise
Programs
Programs/Beach Party, 1997
Programs/General Meetings, 1990s
Programs/Outgoing President's Party, 2000
Programs/Jewish Women of Achievement
Red Cross Parade, 1917
Box 3: S-Z
Thrift Shop/Honorees, 1990s, 2 folders
Trips
Trips/New York National Office
Youth Aliyah Luncheons, 1997, 2 folders
Oversize photos are with Organizations/Oversize
Szold, Henrietta; Hadassah; Jewish Women; Zionism
- Series I: A-Hartford Chapter/Programs/Hand of Healing
  - Hartford Chapter/Certificate for Service to Hartford Member Esther Welk, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/About this collection, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Adeph Book Group, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Anniversaries, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Associates, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Awards and Honors Given, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Awards and Honors Received, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Constitution and By-Laws, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Conventions, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Correspondence, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Fundraising, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Hartford Herzlia /Miscellaneous/, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/History, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Installation/All Divisions, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/JNF Certificates, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/JNF Certificates, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Meeting Invitations 1935-1941, plus misc. (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Membership, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Membership and Officer Lists 1940s-1980s, 1940-1989 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1920s-1930s and undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newspaper clippings 2000s, 2000-2009 (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Programs/Donor, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Programs/Hadassah Medical Organization, undated (Box 1)
  - Hartford Chapter/Programs/Hand of Healing, undated (Box 1)
- Series II: Hartford Chapter/Programs/Miscellaneous-Z
  - Hartford Chapter/Programs/Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
  - Hartford Chapter/Programs/Youth Aliyah, undated (Box 2)
  - Hartford Chapter/Sabbath, undated (Box 2)
  - Hartford Chapter/Thrift Shop, undated (Box 2)
  - Manchester Chapter/History, undated (Box 2)
  - Manchester Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1980s-1990s, 1980-1999 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Chapters in CT/Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 2)
  - National Organization, undated (Box 2)
  - New Britain Chapter/Correspondence, undated (Box 2)
  - New Britain Chapter/History, undated (Box 2)
  - New Britain Chapter/Newsletters, undated (Box 2)
  - New Britain Chapter/Newspaper clippings 1980s, 1990s, 1980-1999 (Box 2)
  - Pyquaug Chapter (Newington, Rocky Hill, Wethersfield)/Newspaper clippings 1980s-1990s, 1980-1999 (Box 2)
  - Vanguard Program for Singles, undated (Box 2)
  - Weddings through the Decades, October 20, 1987 (videocassette) (Box 2)
  - Winter in Natanya Program for Seniors, undated (Box 2)
  - Young Judeans, undated (Box 2)
- Series III: Newsletters, 1930s-1980s
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1930s (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1943 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, `1952 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1987, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1988, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hartford Hadassah Headlines, 1989, 1991 (Box 3)
  - National Newsletters 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 3)
- Series IV: Newsletters
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah; Name changes to Hadassah Bulletin in Nov., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Hartford Chapter/Newsletters/Hadassah Bulletin, 2005 (Box 4)
- Series V: Hartford Chapter/Shopper's Guides
  - Shopper's Guide/1948-1949 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1951-1952 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1952-1953 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1955 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1957 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1957 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1958 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1958 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1959 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1960 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1960 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1961 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1962, 50th anniversary (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1965 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1967 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1968 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1968 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1969 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Guide/1972-1973 (Box 5)
- Photo Series I: A-G
  - Anniversaries, undated (Box 1)
  - Associates, undated (Box 1)
  - Associates/party honoring David Sheketoff, undated (Box 1)
  - Awards, 2 folders, undated (Box 1)
  - Board of Directors, early 20th century, undated (Box 1)
  - Board of Directors, late 20th century, see also OVERSIZE; folder is too large for box, and is on shelf next to the organization/oversize box., undated (Box 1)
  - Board of Directors/Presidents, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - Building/interiors/1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 1)
  - Conferences, undated (Box 1)
  - Conventions, 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 1)
  - Donor Luncheon, undated (Box 1)
- Photo Series II: H-R
  - Hadassah Medical Organization/Big Gifts Dinner, undated (Box 2)
  - Hand of Healing, undated (Box 2)
  - Installations, undated (Box 2)
  - Junior Hadassah, undated (Box 2)
  - Major Gifts Dinner, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders, undated (Box 2)
  - Meetings, undated (Box 2)
  - Membership, undated (Box 2)
  - Membership/Kaplan, Shirlee/Miscellaneous photos from various Hadassah events and meetings, c.1970s-1990s, 1970-1999 (Box 2)
  - National Organization/H. Szold with S.S. Wise, undated (Box 2)
  - Programs, undated (Box 2)
  - Programs/Beach Party, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Programs/General Meetings, 1990s, undated (Box 2)
  - Programs/Outgoing President's Party, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Programs/Jewish Women of Achievement, undated (Box 2)
  - Red Cross Parade, 1917 (Box 2)
- Photo Series III: S-Z
  - Thrift Shop/Honorees, 1990s, 2 folders, 1990-1999 (Box 3)
  - Trips, undated (Box 3)
  - Trips/New York National Office, undated (Box 3)
  - Youth Aliyah Luncheons, 1997, 2 folders (Box 3)